meteorgames.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Meteor Games

The following Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use and any other policies, notices, rules or guidelines posted on the Site shall govern Your use of the Site. Please read this policy carefully since by visiting this Site and/or sharing information with Us, You agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use unless You offer different terms in writing which are accepted by Meteor Games in writing. 

### California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights

Under California law, our customers who are California residents may request information from us concerning Meteor Games’ disclosure of their personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Meteor Games does not share our customer’s personal information with unaffiliated third parties for direct marketing purposes without that customer’s approval.

### TO THE PARENTS OF CHILD USERS UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE: 

Children under 13 years of age are considered by Meteor Games to be underage and are not permitted to register an account with the Site. If you become aware that your underage child has formed an account with any Meteor Games property and you would like the account and its related personal information to be removed, please notify us by e-mail at [Legal@meteorgames.com](mailto:Legal@meteorgames.com) and include your child’s name, account name and e-mail address, but not the account password. Please also include your name and an e-mail address or daytime telephone number where we can reach you directly. Upon receipt of your request, we will initiate steps for the account and information removal as soon as possible. These steps may include contacting you for confirmation. 

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND SHARING PRACTICES

**WHAT DO WE COLLECT? HOW DO WE COLLECT IT?**

When you register for certain Meteor Games services and/or promotions we will ask you to provide certain personally identifiable information (“PII”). For example Users voluntarily provide information such as their age, name and e-mail address upon registration and creation of an Account. We may collect credit card information, Facebook Credits balance, transaction identification numbers, and billing information (including a telephone number) for uses related to payments, fees, or billing. In order to improve your experience with our games and communication with our players, we may collect information relating to Your social network, expressed interests, Facebook “likes,” responses to advertising campaigns for our games, usage statistics for our games (including usage of mini-games within each game), and information about other games You play or applications You use. We may additionally ask questions about preferences through means such as surveys.

We also use standard web technologies such as cookies and web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information (“non-PII”) such as your IP address, browser types, operating systems, domain names, access dates and times, referring website addresses, online transactions and browsing and search activities.

We may combine your data with any other Meteor Games data, including data collected from third parties.

**WHY DO WE COLLECT IT?**

We collect PII to provide the services offered by Meteor Games and/or its affiliates. We collect non-PII to obtain information about your visits to our sites or your responses to e-mail from us – both individually and  
in aggregated data that does not identify you. This information helps us to administer the site and, when linked with PII enables us to better customize your experience on the site.

**SHARING**

We will share Your Information with third party service providers, our subsidiaries and affiliates, with third party marketing partners; or as may be necessary to protect Meteor Games, third parties or as otherwise required to comply with applicable laws, rules and regulations. In particular, Meteor Games may disclose your information if we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by us, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce our terms of use or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the Site.

In the event that Meteor Games is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

By using any of Meteor Games’ services and/or games, You acknowledge that Meteor Games operates in the United State and You agree to (i) permit Meteor Games to transmit and use Your User information anywhere necessary, including across international boundaries, to affect the services and transactions provided by this Site; and (ii) that such use by Meteor Games shall be subject to the terms and conditions stated in this Privacy Statement and our Terms of Use.

All disputes arising under this policy shall be resolved by arbitration before a panel of the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”) in Los Angeles County, California. The arbitration shall be subject to the AAA rules then in effect and enforceable in the state and federal courts in Los Angeles County. Any claims arising under this agreement must be brought in the claimant’s individual capacity, and not as a plaintiff or class member in any purported class or representative proceeding.

**YOUR CHOICES**

We want you to know that you have options with respect to how your information is collected or used. You may contact us at [Legal@meteorgames.com](mailto:Legal@meteorgames.com). to determine whether we have personal data about you and confirm whether it is accurate We will promptly provide you with a readable copy of any personal data which we keep about you without charge, although we may require proof of your identity before processing your request.

**CHANGES**

Meteor Games’ Privacy Policy is prominently posted on the Meteor Games Privacy Policy webpage (www.meteorgames.com/privacy-policy/) and is linked to from all of our games. We will post changes onto the Privacy Policy webpage and by posting an announcement in the Meteor Games Forums. We will retain the on-line announcement for at least 30 days after its posting date. If, however, we change the policy to permit us to use your data in a manner that is materially different from our representations at the time your data was collected, we will provide notice to you via email at the last address provided by you and you will have thirty days to opt-out of such a change.

**SECURITY**

Meteor Games has in place and maintains appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. No transmission of information is guaranteed to be completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise data security. You acknowledge and agree to assume this risk when communicating with Us.

**QUESTIONS**

[privacy@meteorgames.com](mailto:privacy@meteorgames.com). Responses will be restricted to privacy questions or correspondence.
